Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer In Jesus' Name at The SCOAN Prayer Line.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
What?
Leave her.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Leave her. That is simple.
Sometimes you make these demons proud.
Leave her.
The more they become wild and you then grab them, you encourage them to do more.
Where are you? Come out!
1, 2!
Here!
Come here!
1, 2!
What?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer In Jesus' Name at The SCOAN Prayer Line.
Is that not somebody who was ...?
What happened?
I was on the prayer line.
Go back to the prayer line.
You don't know what happened?
You touched me. Then, fire, everywhere.
You mean, I touched you?
I don't know but you touched me.
After touching you, what happened?
I saw fire, everywhere.
Fire everywhere?
Yes.
So what happened to you and fire?
I was feeling very very hot.
Ok, listen to that.
If you are inside fire, you would not run?
That is why, everywhere, everywhere...
"You, T.B.Joshua, you are the one who put me inside the fire!"
So, where is the fire now?
No more fire.
What does the fire look like? Tell us. People want to know.
It was like flames.
Ok, look at me. After touching you, how does it come out?
I don't know; I saw some flames.
Ok. How did I touch you?
Just like this.
There was fire on you. I wanted to come near you but it was...
Can I touch you?
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer In Jesus' Name at The SCOAN Prayer Line
You need to know much about what is actually delivering you.
You need to know much about the power you are under.
You are under power.
You know the power but you still want to know more.
If you know more about the power you are under,
it is much better than just the deliverance and blessing you are receiving.
If you now receive that blessing, you would know how to keep it.
Ok, you are free.
You are free now.
What happened again? You were talking.
Ok, sit down and talk.
There was fire again upon me.
That's the fire that looses and also binds -
whatever that needs to be loosed in your body.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
TT: Mel Flowers
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 17/06/2018